Adriana-Ramona Lazar

Str.Buna Ziua nr.37 Ap.3 ,Cluj-Napoca,Cluj 400495

<u>Adrianaramona.lazar@gmail.com</u>

Ph:0753479109

Professional Summary

Software Consultant with 1-year experience in planning, developing and implementing proprietary software products and integrating documentation projects.

Energetic and results-driven professional with 6 years' experience in customer service area. Successful track record of conferring with customers by telephone and in-person to provide them with information regarding products or services. Strong interpersonal skills, with the ability to relate and empathize with people of varying personalities and from all walks of life. Possesses strong communication and organizational skills. Demonstrated ability to work both independently and as a team member.

Skills

- Computers and electronics
- Economics and accounting
- Critical thinking
- Active listening

- HTML,JavaScript,CSS,WordPress
- Customer and personal service
- English, Hungarian and Spanish language

Experience

Customer Service Representative Yardi Romania

Oct 2017 - present Cluj Napoca, Cluj

- Manage large amount of income calls
- Respond efficiently to customer inquiries and maintain high customer satisfaction
- Follow communication procedures, guidelines and policies
- *Provide accurate, valid and complete information by using the right methods / tools*

- Handle customer complaints, provide appropriate solutions and alternatives
- *Keep records of customer interactions, process customer accounts and file documents.*

Software Consultant/Manual QA Tester Ebriza Softwares

Oct 2016-Aug 2017 Cluj-Napoca, Cluj

- Answer telephones and provide callers with information, take messages or transfer calls to the appropriate individuals.
- Create, maintain and enter information into databases.
- Greet visitors or callers and handle their inquiries or direct them to the appropriate people according to their requirements.
- Design test plans, scenarios, scripts or procedures.
- Test systems modifications to prepare for implementation.
- Document software defects using a bug tracking system and report defects to software developers.
- Participate in product-design reviews to provide input on functional requirements, product designs, schedules or potential problems

Accountant Assistant Mara-Lazar May 2016-Sep 2016 Aiud,Alba

- Calculate taxes owed and prepare tax returns, ensuring compliance with payment, reporting or other tax requirements.
- Prepare, examine or analyze accounting records, financial statements or other financial reports to assess accuracy, completeness and conformance to reporting and procedural standards.
- Compile, sort and verify the accuracy of data before it is entered.
- Read source documents, such as cancelled cheques, sales reports or bills, and enter data into specific data fields, or onto tapes or disks, for subsequent entry using keyboards or scanners.

Education

Diploma: Front End Web Development Sept 2017

Azimut Vision Cluj-Napoca,Cluj

Master of Science: Food Safety and Consumer Protection

Jul 2014

 $USAMV, University\ of\ Agricultural\ Science\ and\ Veterinary\ Medicine\ Cluj-Napoca,\ Cluj$

Bachelor of Science: Accounting and Management Information Systems Jul 2012

UBB,Babes-Bolyai University Cluj-Napoca,Cluj